pressitt.com 2010-11-01

# Pressitt - Privacy

## Protecting your privacy

Pressitt is committed to protecting your privacy. This statement is made in light of the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998 in order to alert you to Pressitt�s data processing practices which will govern the processing of your data. If you have any queries about this statement, please contact us [Click here to contact us](http://pressitt.com/auth/contact "Contact us").

## How do we collect information?

We will obtain personal information about you when you enquire about our services, register with us, post a SMNR using Pressitt, or otherwise provide us with personal information.

## What information do we collect?

The types of information we might collect includes names, addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers and fax numbers.

When you pay for the services of Pressitt, you will be asked for credit card and billing information.

## How do we use your information?

We will use your information to provide you with the information or services you have requested, for administration purposes, for authentication and identification, contact, to further our aims and to comply with the law. At no point will your information be given to any other third parties without your prior permission.

We do not store credit card or billing information.

We may, from time to time, contact you to provide the products and services you have requested, send you communications relating to the Pressitt service, such as administrative messages and service announcements, that are considered part of your Pressitt account.

## How do we protect personal information?

We take appropriate measures to ensure that the information disclosed to us is kept secure, accurate and up to date and kept only for so long as is necessary for the purposes for which it is used.

When you post information that is accessible online using the Pressitt service, you may receive unsolicited messages from third parties that are not associated with the Pressitt service or Pressitt. Pressitt does not share or sell information for commercial purposes.

## Your consent

By providing us with your personal data, you consent to the collection and use of any information you provide in accordance with the above purposes and this privacy statement.
